# Bruno Zurita

#### **IT Professional**

Tucson, AZ zuritabruno2896@gmail.com 5205910163

A successful self-driven individual lookingfor advancement within Information Technology. Experienced System Administrator with three year backgroundin Information Technology. Expert in customer service and security systems. Known for best-in-class hardware and software knowledge and detail-oriented project roll outs. Extensive experience in networking, property systems, leadership, and systems security along with an eagerness to learn newer technology. A fast learner that can adapt to any environment.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

## Work Experience

### **Systems Administrator**

Child Parent Centers, Inc - Tucson, AZ August 2020 to Present

Analyzed intricate server issues and supported large enterprise and business-critical applications. Provided effective resolutions to issues and escalated problems with knowledgeable support and quality service. Provided customer support such as troubleshooting computers, printers, scanners, and phones to users working remotely and on site. Deployed Print Server within the Organization to minimize deployment time for computers. Reconfigured the Deployment Server (Ghost) to be able to reimage computers at faster pace and assist in accomplishing the team's deadlines for deployments. Created script to automate procedures for easier and faster computer set up, like installing agents in the background without any user interaction. Assisting with removing retired devices from Active Directory; general Exchange mailbox issues; Zoom platform assistance. Upgraded Servers from 2012R2 to 2019. Utilize Kace Quest for ticket solutions. Repaired the Apple Server to be able to configure and deploy iPads to multiple centers. Change desk phone names, voicemail pins and rerouting desktop call to cell phones. Troubleshooting VMware with command lines to resolve minor issues with virtual machines. Creating new Virtual Machines as new servers. Upgrade Center and V Sphere from 6.0 to 7.0. Conducted maintenance on ESXi hosts and clusters.

## **Property Systems Lead (Senior Technician)**

Gaylord Opryland Resort and Convention June 2018 to Present

Fostered and maintained collaborative professional working relationship with project leadership team and client. Provide level 2 support for Network and Desktop support remotely andon site for 1,000+ users. Utilized VMware environment to diagnose, monitor and resolve servers to ensure daily tasks were not interrupted by a failing server. Utilized and integrated CommVault software for emergency data back up. Imaged Win 7 and Win 10 computers while following Marriott policies to meet standards. Configured VLANs and ports throughout the network. Assisted Server Administrator by updating patches on the Image server to ensure Images were up to date. In charge of reprogramming Point of Sale(POS)

when applicable, employ full set ups for program deployment, and maintain accurate inventory. Utilized MAARK1.2 to remediate devices that were not meeting policy standard. Given the managerial title for emergency calls such as network outage, certain software application not working due to server failure. Configured active directory users, print server; added, removed and modified printers; and added permissions for users and computers through active directory.

### **Information Technology Technician**

U.S Army - Fort Campbell, KY July 2014 to April 2018

Diagnose, troubleshoot software, and other system issues. Monitored equipment and notified proper personnel to correct problems. Provided training to personnel on proper procedures and protocols to meet the standard for system security including phishing, trojan virus, and basic equipment standards. Maintained workplace safety by involving employees in order to maximize engagement and team morale. Worked closely with Battalion S-6 to provide established Secure and Unsecured networks for missions, which included VoIP via Satellite. Monitored daily operations and performed safety audits to check that staff followed administrative policies and regulations.

#### Education

## High school diploma in Information Technology of Systems Administration

**Technical School** 

2018

## Skills

- · Technical Skills
- Secret Clearance
- Troubleshooting
- Firewall & Security
- Linux
- Operating Systems
- Azure
- TCP/IP & DNS/DHCP
- LAN / WAN
- Active Directory
- Networking
- Servers
- · Remote Desktop
- System Administration
- VoIP
- · Microsoft Windows
- Microsoft Windows Server
- · Network Monitoring

- Network Support
- Disaster Recovery
- VMWare
- Microsoft Exchange
- SQL
- PowerShell

# Military Service

**Branch: United States Army** Service Country: United States

Rank: Specialist

July 2014 to April 2018

## Certifications and Licenses

## **Secret Clearance**